{
    "subject": "resource/Joaquin_Phoenix",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Puerto_Rico",
    "human_readable": "Joaquin Phoenix was born in Puerto Rico.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9010691046714783,
            "question": "Where was Joaquin Phoenix born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8007115125656128,
            "question": "What year was Joaquin Phoenix born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6708137392997742,
            "question": "What is Joaquin Phoenix's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4312535524368286,
            "question": "Who are some of Joaquin Phoenix's siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41663381457328796,
            "question": "Is Joaquin Phoenix known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2875595688819885,
            "question": "Is Joaquin Phoenix known for any particular acting style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2302982211112976,
            "question": "Has Joaquin Phoenix won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19458025693893433,
            "question": "What type of roles is Joaquin Phoenix known for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16568930447101593,
            "question": "Has Joaquin Phoenix ever directed a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15267513692378998,
            "question": "What movies has Joaquin Phoenix starred in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joaquin Phoenix was born in Puerto Rico.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5890_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Joaquin Phoenix ever directed a film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5890_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of roles is Joaquin Phoenix known for playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5890_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Joaquin Phoenix won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5890_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5890_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5890_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5890_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5890_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5890_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5890_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5890_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5890_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5890_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5890_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The birthplace of Joaquin Phoenix is mentioned as San Juan, Puerto Rico, and also R\u00edo Piedras, a sector of the city of San Juan, Puerto Rico."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Joaquin Phoenix was born in San Juan, Puerto Rico. Therefore, the statement \"Joaquin Phoenix was born in Puerto Rico\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}